Guide to the Stanford University, Government and Community Relations, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Government and Community Relations, records
1977-1997
SC0568
Stanford University. Government and Community Relations
44 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
20 yr restriction applies
Access Terms
Stanford University -- General subdivision--Finance.;; Federal aid to research--Overhead costs.
Collection Contents
- Records
  - Stanford's Research Policy Handbook (Box 1)
  - Medical Progress: A Miracle at Risk (Box 1)
  - Cost Accounting Standards Board Disclosure Statement (July 1995) (Box 1)
  - Analysis of False Claims Act at Stanford University (Box 1)
  - Financial Responsibility at Universities (Box 1)
  - Decanal Indirect Cost Study (Box 1)
  - Congressional Hearing Transcript (Box 1)
  - Science Subcommittee Hearings (April 21-23, 1995) (Box 1)
  - Sponsored Projects Report for the Year Ended Aug. 31, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Memorandum of Understanding between Federal Government and Stanford University, Vol. I and II (2 copies each) (Box 2)
  - Stanford University Response to DCAA Audit Report Number 7311-90V43510004 (0353) (Box 2)
  - "DCAA Report on Review of SU Library Studies and Related Office of Naval Research Studies", Vol. I and II (Box 2)
  - DCAA's Involvement in Memoranda of Understanding, Special Studies and Negotiations at SU, Commentary and Documents (Box 2)
  - Report Inquiry into SU Overhead Rates (2) (Box 3)
  - Special Advisory Panel to SU: Standards of Accountability - Federal Research Costs (Box 3)
  - Auditing Expenditures and Negotiating I-C Rates for Government Funded Research and Other Activities at Universities: An Options Paper for the A21 Task Force (Box 3)
  - Tuition Remission for Graduate Research Assistants (Box 3)
  - Janet's IDC collection (Box 3)
  - Response to MOU Audits 6/31/92 (3) (Box 4)
  - Cost Policy and Chart of Accounts (Box 4)
  - SU Efforts to Seek Audits (April 1991) (Box 4)
  - DCAA/MOUS, studies/negotiations (Box 4)
  - Doc. No. 413 (April 8, 1911) (Box 4)
  - Library Study (Vol. I and II) (Box 4)
  - Document #120 (Box 4)
  - Federal Research (System for Reimbursing Universities' Indirect Costs Should be Reevaluated) (Box 4)
  - SEMATECH Program (Box 4)
  - University Research, Controlling Inappropriate Access (Box 4)
  - Small Business Research (Box 4)
  - Congressional Report (June - August 1992) (Box 4)
  - Task Force Member Reports (CA fiscal reform) - recommendations/summary (Box 4)
  - Stanford Magazine (July/August 1997 (Box 4)
  - Campus Plan for Second Century (Box 4)
  - Indirect Cost Review - Larry Horton - #1245-1301 (Box 5)
  - Indirect Cost Review - Larry Horton - #1302-1370 (Box 5)
  - Indirect Cost Review - Larry Horton - #1171-1244 (Box 5)
  - Indirect Cost Review - Larry Horton - #1-82 (Box 5)
  - Papers: Selected Materials; Prepared Statements; Controller's Office Efforts; Transcripts of Hearings; Arthur Anderson Review (Box 5)
  - Special Addresses (Box 6)
  - Interim Report on Implementation of Internal Control Recommendations Related to Federal Contracts & Grants March 31, 1992 (2) (Box 6)
  - Economic Impact, Yale & New Haven (Box 6)
  - Stanford University Response to DCAA Audits for 1981-88, Vol. I thru VII (Box 6)
  - Stanford University Response to DCAA Report on Proposed Overhead Rates 1991-92 (Box 6)
  - Indirect Cost Review - Larry Horton - #1146-1170 (Box 7)
  - Indirect Cost Review - Larry Horton - # 1078-1145 (Box 7)
  - Indirect Cost Review - Larry Horton - #788-863 (Box 7)
  - Indirect Cost Review - Larry Horton - #741-787 (Box 7)
  - Indirect Cost Recovery April 7, 1982 (Box 7)
  - FY92 Indirect Cost Rate Proposal (Box 7)
  - Congressional Subcommittee Hearings IDC, May 9, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Transcript January 21, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Congressional Subcommittee on Environment, Energy & Natural Resources Request, August 28, 1991 (Box 8)
  - GAO questions and lists (Box 8)
  - DMT's Hoover, Hanna, Lake houses (Box 8)
  - Report on Agreed-Upon Procedures with Respect to Internal Audit Report #995 (Box 8)
  - Report on Review of Internal Controls Related to Federal Contracts/Grants (Box 8)
  - Interim Report on Implementation of Internal Control Recommendations (Box 8)
  - Stanford University FY81 - FY88 Audit Response, ONR Presentation (Box 8)
  - Claim by Board of Trustees for Indirect Costs of Research (Box 8)
  - Armed Services Board of Contract Appeals Statement of Jurisdiction (Box 8)
  - Files:
    - CRS issue brief (Box 9)
    - Budget (Box 9)
    - GAO/IDC (Box 9)
    - COGR comparative IDC (Box 9)
    - IDC contract proposal (Box 9)
    - Slides (Box 9)
    - Basic Research Info (Box 9)
    - Basic Research (Box 9)
    - A-21 (Box 9)
    - A-21 Revision 1992-93 (Box 9)
    - 20/20 Transcripts (Box 9)
    - Clnton 44% Cut - IDC (Box 9)
    - Conflict of interest (Box 9)
    - Tax stuff (Box 9)
    - IDC/Clnton budget March 1993 (Box 9)
    - Biddle (Box 9)
  - Binders:
    - FY92 and FY93 Indirect Cost Proposals (Box 9)
    - Press IV (Box 9)
  - Report of the White House Science Council (Box 10)
  - Financing/Managing University Research Equipment (Box 10)
  - IC Associated with Federal Support of Research University Campuses (Box 10)
  - Analysis of Selected Federally Prescribed Research Administration Activities (Box 10)
  - The Indirect Cost Binder (Box 10)
  - Science & Tech transfer: (Box 10)
  - Stanford Complete Briefing Book with Attachments (VI) (Box 10)
  - VCU Chron Oct 1988 (I and II) (Box 10)
  - Indirect Cost Review - Larry Horton - #709-740 (Box 11)
  - Indirect Cost Review - Larry Horton - #905-1000 (Box 11)
  - Indirect Cost Review - Larry Horton - #1001-1077 (Box 11)
  - Indirect Cost Review - Larry Horton - #864-904 (Box 11)
  - Booklets re: Prepared Statements Hearings; Indirect Cost Analysis (Box 11)
  - Press Articles (Box 12)
  - SU FY81-FY88 Audit Response; ONR Presentation (Box 12)
  - SU Interim Report on Implementation of Internal Control Recommendations Related to Federal Contracts and Grants (3 copies) (Box 12)
  - SU Report on Review of Internal Controls Related to Federal Contracts and Grants (5 copies) (Box 12)
  - Sponsored Projects Report for the Year Ended Aug. 31, 1989 (Box 12)
  - Sponsored Projects Report for the Year Ended Aug. 31, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Hearing On Indirect Charges at Stanford, 3/13/91 (Box 12)
  - Indirect Cost Study, 1987, 1988 (Box 12)
  - Prepared Statements: Indirect Costs at SU 3/13/91 (Box 12)
  - Selected Materials Relating to Indirect Cost (Box 12)
  - Federal research pamphlets (Box 12)
  - Summary/Req. of Proposals to Meet Research Facilities Needs on College Campuses (Box 12)
  - Funding by DoD (Box 12)
  - Binders:
    - Sidebottom (current) (Box 13)
    - Sidebottom (April 89/November 89) (Box 13)
    - Sidebottom (November 88/March 89) (Box 13)
    - Sidebottom (June 88/October 88) (Box 13)
    - Rob Eno's Chron, Part I (Box 13)
  - Binders:
    - IDC Press Clippings, 1-279 to 3/8/91 (Box 14)
    - IDC Press Clippings II (Box 14)
    - IDC Press Clippings III (Box 14)
  - DCAA's Involvement in memoranda of Understanding, Special Studies and Negotiations at Stanford University - Commentary and Documents (4 copies) (Box 15)
  - SU Response to DCAA Audit Report #7311-90U43510004 (0353) Vol. I (Box 15)
  - Report on the White House Science Council (Box 15)
  - Stanford's Active Efforts to Seek Audits from DCAA - Commentary and Documents (5 copies) (Box 15)
  - Indirect Costs Associated with Federal Support of Research on University Campuses: Some Suggestions for Change (Box 15)
  - Utility Cost Allocation Study (Box 15)
  - Prepared Statements: Hearing of the House Subcommittee on Oversight and Investigations Committee on Energy: Comments on Indirect Charges at Stanford University (3/13/91) (Box 15)
  - Federal Support of Project Grants: Indirect Cost and Cost Sharing: Hearings (2 copies) (Box 15)
  - SU, A Program to Reform Financial Controls in Federally Sponsored Research, Stage 3, October 1991 (5 copies) (Box 15)
  - Special Advisory Panel to SU: Standards of Accountability - Fed. Research Costs (Box 15)
  - DCAA's Involvement (Box 16)
  - Mercury News FOIA Releases (Box 16)
  - Standards of Accountability Federal Research Costs (Box 16)
  - Financial Responsibility at Universities (Box 16)
  - IDC Press Index (Box 16)
  - IDC Review Withdrawals (Box 16)
  - Appendix to Memorandum of Stanford in Support of Request for Advisory Opinion and Other Relief (Supplement: Appendix) (Box 17)
  - Trustee Oversight Committee on IDC (Box 17)
  - IDC Settlement Press (Box 17)
  - IDC Management Team (Box 17)
  - Indirect Cost Study Schedules (Box 17)
  - Summary of Assumptions, Methodologies, Definitions, and Changes from Previous Years (Box 17)
  - Original transcript, 3/13/91 (Box 17)
  - FY 91 IDC claim (Box 17)
  - AD Hoc Committee on IDC (Box 17)
  - SU FY 95-96: Indirect Cost Proposal, Staff Benefits Proposal (Box 18)
  - FY 92 IDC Cost Rate Proposal (Box 18)
  - FY 95-96 Indirect Cost Proposal (binder) (Box 18)
  - AF-12/Madey (Box 18)
  - Staff Benefits D.M.T.'s (Box 18)
  - Larry Horton 83-164 (Box 18)
  - Staff Benefit Proposals (Box 18)
  - Judiciary Subcommittee Hearing on Qui Tam suits (Box 18)
  - Indirect Cost Analysis (Box 18)
  - Indirect Cost Waivers (Box 18)
  - Indirect Cost Analysis (Box 18)
  - Binders:
    - Fraud in Research Rule-making 10/88 (Box 19)
    - Conference Tax Binder General (Box 19)
    - Conference Tax Binder Ap P/B etc. (Box 19)
    - Senate Tax Binder General (Box 19)
  - Folders:
    - Ken Bloem/Molly Coye meeting 12/12/92 Briefing Book (Box 19)
    - Korn testimony 3/28/90 (Box 19)
  - Binders:
    - Senate Tax (Box 20)
    - After the Tax Bill (Box 20)
    - Report on IDC Waivers 1989-90 FY (Box 20)
    - SU FY 1994 and 1995 IDC Proposals (Box 20)
  - Binders:
    - Indirect Cost Review - Larry Horton vol. III (#165-246) (Box 21)
    - Indirect Cost Review - Larry Horton vol. IV (#247-323) (Box 21)
    - Indirect Cost Review - Larry Horton vol. V (#324-387) (Box 21)
  - Binders:
    - Indirect Cost Review - Larry Horton vol. VI (# 388-450) (Box 22)
    - Indirect Cost Review - Larry Horton vol. VII (# 451-514) (Box 22)
    - Photocopies of articles from PA Weekly on Indirect Costs 1992 (2) (Box 22)
    - Selected Materials Relating to Indirect Costs Prepared for Members of the Advisory Panel on Standards on Accountability, 1991 (5 copies) (Box 22)
    - Loma Prieta Earthquake Damage at SU and Repairs Required by Applicable Codes; Background Material... for FEMA, 1992 (2 copies) (Box 22)
  - Binders:
    - Documents #1371-1407 (Box 23)
    - Documents #1409-1440 (Box 23)
    - Documents #1441-1458 (Box 23)
    - Documents #1459-1468 (Box 23)
  - Five binders on tax reform (Box 24)
  - Loose miscellaneous folders (Box 24)
  - Binders:
    - Earthquake 89, Part 1 (Box 25)
    - Earthquake 89, Part 2 (Box 25)
    - Tax Reform (Bonds) (Box 25)
    - Benefits (Box 25)
  - Binders:
    - Stanford Complete Briefing Book with Attachments, I (Box 26)
    - Stanford Complete Briefing Book with Attachments, III (Box 26)
    - Unlabelled [various SU/government documents] (Box 26)
  - Folders:
    - Harvard Research (Box 26)
    - Stanford Research (Box 26)
    - MIT Research (Box 26)
  - Binders: (Box 27)
    - Appeal to the Regional Director of FEMA Region IX [re geology corner damage], 1993 (Box 27)
    - FEMA (Box 27)
    - IDC Anthologies/Indices (Box 27)
  - Folders: (Box 27)
    - Earthquake Special Session November 1989 (Box 27)
    - Damaged buildings maps (Box 27)
  - Binders:
    - Indirect Cost Review - Larry Horton vol. VIII 515-583 (May 91 - June 91) (Box 28)
    - Indirect Cost Review - Larry Horton vol. IX 584-650 (July 1991) (Box 28)
    - Indirect Cost Review - Larry Horton vol. X 651 - 708 (Aug. 1 - Sept. 11, 1991) (Box 28)
  - Audio/Visual Materials:
    - Stanford Alumni Association, D. Kennedy Speech in Senate Caucus Room, 2/19/91 (VHS) (Box 28)
    - 20/20 Lead-in and story only (VHS) (Box 28)
    - Bay Area Newsmakers - KQED Tape off Air (VHS) (Box 28)
    - News Coverage of Stanford Hearings 3/13 - 3/14/91 (VHS) (Box 28)
  - Binders:
    - Book 13 Memoranda of Understanding between SU and US Government (Box 29)
    - IDC Press Releases V (Box 29)
    - IDC Press Releases VI (Box 29)
  - Audio/Visual Materials:
    - Biddle on KGO, 1/7/92 (audio cassette) (Box 29)
    - KQED - Biddle 9/25/92 (audio cassette) (Box 29)
    - House Committee Hearings: GAO Testimony I, GAO Testimony II, GAO/DCAA Testimony, DCAA/ONR Testimony, ONR Testimony, Stanford Testimony (7 VHS tapes) (Box 29)
    - C-SPAN - House Committee Hearings (9 VHS tapes) (Box 29)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1999-172
  - Stanford's Research Policy Handbook 1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Medical Progress: A Miracle at Risk 1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cost Accounting Standards Board Disclosure Statement 7/1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Analysis of False Claims Act at SU 1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Financial Responsibility at Universities hearings 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Decanal Indirect Cost (IDC) Study 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Congressional Hearing Transcript (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Science Subcommittee Hearings 4/21-23/1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Sponsored Projects Report for the Year Ending Aug. 31, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda of Understanding (MOU) between Federal Government and SU, Vol. I and II (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Response to DCAA (Defense Contract Audit Agency) Audit Report Number 7311-90V43510004 (0353) "DCAA Report on Review of SU Library Studies and Related Office of Naval Research Studies", Vol. I (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Response to DCAA Audit Report Number 7311-90V43510004 (0353) "DCAA Report on Review of SU Library Studies and Related Office of Naval Research Studies", Vol. II (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - DCAA's Involvement in Memoranda of Understanding, Special Studies and Negotiations at SU, Commentary and Documents 1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Report of Inquiry into SU Overhead Rates 1/1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Special Advisory Panel to SU: Standards of Accountability - Federal Research Costs (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Auditing Expenditures and Negotiating I-C Rates for Government Funded Research and Other Activities at Universities: An Options Paper for the A21 Task Force 7/1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Tuition Remission for Graduate Research Assistants (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - ONR correspondence, reports, memoranda (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - IDC Collection of Janet Sweet, Assistant Controller (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Response to MOU Audits 6/31/92 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - SU Response to Procedures Related to DCAA 6/18/1991 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Cost Policy and Chart of Accounts 1991 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - SU Efforts to Seek Audits 4/1991 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - DCAA Memoranda of Understanding Studies/Negotiations 4/9/1991 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Document 413 4/8/1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Document 120 10/1990 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - U.S. GAO (Government Accounting Office) Reports: Federal Research; SEMATECH Program; University Research; Controlling Inappropriate Access; Small Business Research 3-9/1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Congressional Report 6-8/1992 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - California Fiscal Reform Task Force Member Report- Recommendations/Summary (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Magazine Vol.24 No.4 7-8/1997 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Campus Plan for Second Century 6/1991 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Horton IDC Review I; 1-82 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Horton IDC Review XIV; 1171-1244 6-7/1993 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Horton IDC Review XX; 1245-1301 7/1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Horton IDC Review XXI; 1302-1370 7-8/1993 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Arthur Anderson & Co. Interim Report 3/1992 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Information Distributed to U.S. GAO at Conference 10/1990 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Selected Materials Related to IDC 1/1999 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Stanford's Active Efforts to Seek Audits from DCAA 4/1991 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - IDC Hearing - Prepared Statements 4/1991 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - IDC Hearing -Transcript 4/1991 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Special Addresses- Trustees, Etc. 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 1 Special Addresses- Trustees, Etc. 1996-1999)
  - Arthur Anderson & Co. Interim Report on Implementation of Internal Control Recommendations Related to Federal Contracts & Grants 3/31/1992 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Economic Impact Study, Yale & New Haven 12/1993 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - SU Response to DCAA Report on Proposed Overhead Rates 1991-92 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - SU Response to DCAA Audits for 1981-88, Vol. I - III (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - SU Response to DCAA Audits for 1981-88, Vol. IV-VI (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - SU Response to DCAA Audits for 1981-88, Vol. VII (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - IDC Recovery 4/7/1982 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - SU FY92 Indirect Cost Rate Proposal 7/1991 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Horton IDC Review XVIII; 1146-1170 1-5/1993 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Horton IDC Review XVII; 1078-1145 9-12/1992 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Horton IDC Review XIII; 788-863 "pre-hearing"12/1991-1/1992 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Horton IDC Review XII; 741-787 10-11/1991 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Congressional Subcommittee Hearings IDC, 5/9/1991 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Transcript 1/21/1992 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Congressional Subcommittee on Environment, Energy & Natural Resources Request, 8/28/1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - U.S. GAO Questions and Lists (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Hoover, Hanna, Lake Houses DMT's (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Coopers & Lybrand Report on Agreed-Upon Procedures with Respect to Internal Audit Report #995 9/1991 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Arthur Anderson & Co. Report on Review of Internal Controls Related to Federal Contracts & Grants; Draft 6/12/1991& Final 7/15/1991 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - SU FY81 - FY88 Audit Response, ONR Presentation 7/15/1991 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Claim by Board of Trustees for Indirect Costs of Research 8/1992 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Armed Services Board of Contract Appeals Statement of Jurisdiction 1/27/1992 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - CRS Issue Brief 4/1992 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Budget Documents: Graphics (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - GAO/IDC (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - COGR Comparative IDC (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - IDC Contract Proposal 5/1993 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - IDC Slides (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - IDC Basic Research Information (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - A-21 (Box 12, Folder 13 A-21)
  - A-21 Revision 1992-93 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 20/20 Transcripts (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Clinton 44% Cut (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Conflict of Interest (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Tax Stuff (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - IDC/Clinton Budget 3/1993 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Biddle (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - SU FY92-93 Indirect Cost Proposals 7/6/1992, Supplement 7/13/1992 (Box 14, Folder 1 SU FY92-93 Indirect Cost Proposals 7/6/1992, Supplement 7/13/1992)
  - IDC Press Releases IV; 830 8/15/1991 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Report of the White House Science Council 2/1986 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Financing/Managing University Research Equipment 1985 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - IDC Associated with Federal Support of Research University Campuses 12/1988 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Analysis of Selected Federally Prescribed Research Administration Activities 4/1987 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Indirect Cost Binder (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Science & Technology Transfer Including: Simplified/Standardized Model Agreements for University-Industry Cooperative Research; Trends in Tech Transfer at Universities Report: AAU; Free Electron Research Center; California Engineering Center Action Agenda for Competitiveness (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - SU Complete Briefing Book with Attachments VI (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Velina Underwood (Office of Public Affairs) Chronological 10/1988 I and II (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Horton IDC Review XI; 709-740 9-10/1991 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Horton IDC Review XV; 905-1000 2-5/1992 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Horton IDC Review XVI; 1001-1077 5-8/1992 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Horton IDC Review XIV; 864-904 1-3/1992 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Hearings Prepared Statements 3/13/1991 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Indirect Cost Analysis Schedules 1/1994 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Press Articles, Correspondence & Information on Biddle (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - SU FY81-FY88 Audit Response; ONR Presentation 7/15/1992 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Sponsored Projects Report for the Year Ending Aug. 31, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Sponsored Projects Report for the Year Ending Aug. 31, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Hearing On Indirect Charges at Stanford, 3/13/91 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Indirect Cost Studies 1987, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Selected Materials Relating to Indirect Cost 1/22/1991 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Federal Research Pamphlets (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Summary/Req. of Proposals to Meet Research Facilities Needs on College Campuses 4/13/1987 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Peter Sidebottom (Assistant Director for Government Relations) Chronological (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Sidebottom Chronological 4-11/1989 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Sidebottom Chronological 11/1988-3/1989 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Sidebottom Chronological 6-10/1988 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Rob Eno (Office of Public Affairs) Chronological I (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - IDC Press Releases I; 1-279 3/8/91 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - IDC Press Releases II; 280-584 3-5/1991 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - IDC Press Releases III; 585-829 5-7/1991 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Stanford's Active Efforts to Seek Audits from DCAA - Commentary and Documents (Box 21, Folder 3 Stanford's Active Efforts to Seek Audits from DCAA - Commentary and Documents)
  - Indirect Costs Associated with Federal Support of Research on University Campuses: Some Suggestions for Change (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Utility Cost Allocation Study (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Hearing of the House Subcommittee on Oversight and Investigations Committee on Energy: Comments on Indirect Charges at Stanford University 3/13/91 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Federal Support of Project Grants: Indirect Cost and Cost Sharing: Hearings I & II (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - SU Program to Reform Financial Controls in Federally Sponsored Research, Stage 3 10/1991 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Special Advisory Panel to SU: Standards of Accountability - Fed. Research Costs (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - DCAA's Involvement Draft (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Mercury News FOIA Releases 1990 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - SU Special Advisory Panel- Standards of Accountability Federal Research Costs (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Hearing- Financial Responsibility at Universities U.S. GAO Serial 102-33 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - IDC Press Index 1986-1994 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - IDC Review Withdrawals 1991 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Memorandum of SU in Support of Request for Advisory Opinion and Other Relief Supplement, Appendix 1991 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Trustee Oversight Committee on IDC (Box 23, Folder 6 Trustee Oversight Committee on IDC)
  - IDC Settlement Press 1994 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - IDC Management Team (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - SU FY89 Indirect Cost Study Schedules (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - SU FY89, FY91 Summary of Assumptions, Methodologies, Definitions, and Changes from Previous Years (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Original Hearing Transcript 3/13/91 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - SU FY91 IDC claim (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Ad Hoc Advisory Committee on IDC (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - SU FY95-96: Indirect Cost Proposal 5/30/1994 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - AF-12, John Madey (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Staff Benefits DMTs & IDC Cost Waiver FY89-90 5/16/1991 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - House Judiciary Subcommittee Hearing on Qui Tam suits 4/1/1992 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Horton IDC Review II; 83-164 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - SU FY95-96 Staff Benefits Proposals #24 6/7/1994 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - SU FY90 IDC Study #32 1/1993 (Box 26, Folder 3)